It's the year 2024!
Ta-da!
The dressing room is decorated like this!
It was so much fun to spend this New Year's Eve with the members and Mr. Sark!
I look forward to seeing you all in 2024!
Thank you very much!
I went to Small's!
I'm going to open a fortune!
I'm going to open the fortune!
It's KICCHI!
Last year, 2023, was also KICCHI!
Oh, by the way...
Let's see...
It says something really good.
I'm going to make my own discoveries in my work.
I'm going to discover things and do my best!
Bye bye!
Happy New Year!
This is Masmatkira.
I slept during the New Year's holidays.
January 1st
I slept all day.
I didn't go out on the 3rd
I had the best New Year's Day like this!
Yes, I did.
Since we're here...
Please take a look at our cute Peta-chan!
This is Akane.
Isn't she cute?
Say hello to everyone!
Here you go.
Good night.
I wish you a Happy New Year.
Okane-chan wants to lose weight this year.
She's a bit of a glutton.
She eats a lot.
Her armpits are so flabby.
Also, she tried her best to shed her skin yesterday, but...
But there was a little bit of skin left on my hand.
I'm going to take it off gently later.
This is Moria-chan.
He's a boy, even though he's called Moria-chan.
He says his goal this year is to train his muscles.
Right?
Unlike Akane, Moria-chan is a bit different.
Sorry I scared you.
He's a quiet boy.
She's a little scaredy-cat.
Each one of them has a different personality.
Just like the members of Sakurazaka.
I look forward to working with you again this year.
I look forward to working with you!
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
One.
Wow.
We're ringing in the new year together.
Yes, yes, yes.
Good night.
Glad to hear it!
Best regards!
Best wishes for the year 2024!
Congratulations!
I am now in Korea!
Twice!
I came here to eat ramen at Hangang
I came to choose my ramen!
I'll eat it!
I would like to give a shout out to the members!
There's a little bit of gong on this one.
I bought this lemon separately.
I'd like to give it to the members here because they're all working so hard
Hello, I'm Yui Takemoto
This New Year's Day...
I've got the Sakura Mimatsu New Year's party coming up, and...
I also had a lot of things I wanted to focus on, so...
So I spent New Year's in Tokyo for the first time without any restrictions!
But my family, my relatives and I get together for New Year's every year.
We have a bingo tournament and play cards.
There is a rock-paper-scissors tournament that is the most exciting event every year.
I participated in it remotely.
I kept playing rock-paper-scissors-scissors with everyone on the videoconference.
It was a really fun New Year's Day.
Seeing everyone's faces made me want to do my best again this year.
Until the day I see my family again
I'm going to work hard until I can see my family again.
That's how I feel about New Year's.
Thank you for watching!
Happy New Year!
My name is Marino Kosaka.
I didn't go back to my parents' house this year.
I haven't been able to do anything New Year's-like this year.
I happened to walk down the street and found a gacha-gacha
I happened to find a gacha-gacha (a gadget that can do fortune-telling)
So I did it!
It was a medium lucky one!
There was a cat holding a fortune.
It's so cute!
I hope I can make 2024 a happy year for you.
I wish you all the best!
Bye bye!
Hi, I'm Rena Morie!
I'm going to draw a fortune now!
So I've drawn my fortune, so I'd like to take a look at it.
I'd like to see it!
Last year it was today, so I'm a little nervous this year
so I'm a little nervous this year.
but I hope it will be a good one.
I'll take a look.
Oh?
Kichi.
How's Kichi?
Not good.
Subtle.
I'm the first girl this year.
No, no, no. New Year's Eve.
I'm the New Year's Girl.
Since I am the woman of the year, I hope to make it a wonderful year.
I will do my best this year.
I look forward to working with you all!
Tenpan
I'm throwing it.
Delicious!
Thank you for watching!
Hello. I am Shizuki Yamashita, a student of Sakurazaka 463rd term.
I didn't do anything in terms of how to spend New Year's.
I didn't do anything in particular during New Year's.
I spent it very slowly and leisurely.
If there is one thing that is typical of New Year's, it is this.
I ate rice cakes.
I like rice cakes.
I wish you all the best in 2024!
This is Reina Odagura, Sakurazaka 463rd year student.
Good evening.
We are almost to the year 2024!
In 2023, I met you all for the first time around the beginning of January.
I think it was a year in which I was able to try many new things throughout the year.
When I look back on my memories and photos
When I look back on my memories and photos, I can't help but smile.
I can't help but smile naturally.
Thank you very much.
I hope that 2024 will be another year of good health and that I can bring you all a lot of happiness.
I wish you all the best in 2024!
I'm thinking of going to Hatsumode (New Year's visit to a shrine) now!
I draw a fortune every year.
I draw a fortune every year
But I can't seem to get any good luck.
I hope to get a big lucky one this year!
I want to make it a good year
I want to start the year with a good one.
Well, I'm off!
It's been 20 minutes since the new year began.
It's been about 20 minutes.
The backstage is like this.
like this backstage.
Thank you very much, manager!
So everyone is getting ready to leave.
I'm ready to go home.
I'm ready to go home, too.
I would like to introduce our catering service.
I would like to introduce our catering.
I think many of our caterers are quite manly.
Sushi
This is YouTube at the end of the year!
And Matsuda!
He looks so manly today with his hair.
I'm in beautiful love today.
Omotosai
Thank you very much
Please do your best again next year
I wish you all the best.
Please keep up the good work
Please keep up the good work!
Please keep up the good work.
Please do your best
Keep up the good work!
It's YouTube at the end of the year
By the way
At the end of the year
That's perfect.
Of course, you all ate it, right?
By the way, I like this one.
It's delicious.
That's how I want to go home.
Okay, just one more couple.
How was it?
Yes, I'm...
I'm the nightlife guy.
Yeah, it was cool.
I didn't see the show, but...
I didn't see the show.
But I did see the rehearsal.
Practice?
I got to perform in Idol.
It was a lot of fun.
It was fun?
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
But I was so busy.
You're flabbergasted, aren't you?
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun.
I'm glad you liked it, and your hair looks great.
It's lovely.
I'm just saying.
You have fair skin.
You're going to tell me what you think?
No, I don't want you to.
Well, thank you very much, and I'll do my best this year and next.
I look forward to working with you.
Bye.
Thank you for watching.